
export const htmlQuestion = [
    {},
    {
        question:  "What does HTML stand for?",
        options: ["Hyper Text Make Language", "High Text Making Language", "Hyper Text Markup Langauge", "High Text-Marking Lingo"],
        answer: 'Hyper Text Markup Langauge'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the largest HTML heading element',
        options: ['<h6>', '<body>', '<h1>', '<heading>'],
        answer: '<h1>'
    },
    {
        question: 'How can you make a numbered list?',
        options: ['<ul>', '<list>', '<numList>', '<ol>'],
        answer: '<ol>'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?',
        options: ['<br>', '<break>', '<newLine>', '<breakPoint>'],
        answer: '<br>'
    },
    {
        question: "HTML doesn't allow styling...",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these elements is NOT apart of the table element?',
        options: ['<tr>', '<th>', '<td>', '<a>'],
        answer: '<a>'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which is the correct HTML for adding a checkbox?',
        options: ['<input type="check">', '<input>checkbox</input>', '<input type="checkbox">', '<check>'],
        answer: '<input type="checkbox">'
    },
    {
        question: 'It is only possible to display photos in JavaScript...',
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: 'Which is the correct to start and end a HTML comment?',
        options: ['<-- -->', '<->', '<!-- -->'],
        answer: '<!-- -->'
    },
    {
        question: 'Styling is only possible through CSS...',
        options: ['True', 'False'],
        answer: 'False'
    },
]

export const cssQuestion = [
    {},
    {
        question: "What does CSS stand for?",
        options: ["Cascading Style Sheets", "Cirling Styling Sheet", "Common Sufficient Sheets", "Cleve Styling Software"],
        answer: "Cascading Style Sheets"
    },
    {
        question: "We can only select 1 class/ id at a time?",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Where in a HTML document is the correct place to refer to a CSS file?",
        options: ["<head>", "<body>", "End of HTML file"],
        answer: "<head"
    },
    {
        question: "Which is the correct syntax?",
        options: ["body = {color = white}", "body; color; white", "body { color: white }", "body = color : white"],
        answer: "body { color: white }"
    },
    {
        question: "Which is the correct way to insert a comment?",
        options: ["<!-- -->", "/* */", "// \\", "'! !'"],
        answer: "/* */"
    },
    {
        question: "Styling is ONLY possible through css...",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "How do we target class names and IDs?",
        options: [".class / #id", "!class / >id", "-class / Â£id", "#class / .id"],
        answer: ".class / #id"
    },
    {
        question: "Creating HTML elements is possible with CSS...",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "When using the padding property; we can only use positive values?",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "Which is correct to change the Font name?",
        options: ["font-change...", "Font-Style...", "font-family...", "change-font..."],
        answer: "font-family.."
    },
]

export const jsQuestion = [
    {},
    {
        question: "What is the short abbreviation for JavaScript?",
        options: ["JST", "JS", "Java", "JScript"],
        answer: "JS",
    },
    {
        question: "How do we link a JavaScript file?",
        options: ["<script>", "<js>", "<Link>", "<JavaScript>"],
        answer: "<script>",
    },
    {
        question: "Where is the correct place to insert JavaScript",
        options: ["The <head> section", "It's not needed!", "The <body> section"],
        answer: "The <head> section",
    },
    {
        question: "Which is the correct use for if statements?",
        options: ["if i == 5...", "if(i == 5)", "if; i == 5", "i == 5 (if)"],
        answer: "",
    },
    {
        question: "When is a if statement executed?",
        options: ["if condition is truthy", "it always executes", "it never executes"],
        answer: "if condition if truthy",
    },
    {
        question: "How do we write to the console?",
        options: ["Console.log()", "alert()", "Console.WriteLine()", "Console.Write()"],
        answer: "Console.log()",
    },
    {
        question: "How do you create a new element using JavaScript?",
        options: ["document.createDiv()", "createDivInDocument()", "document.createElement()", "js.makeNewElement()"],
        answer: "document.createElement()"
    },
    {
        question: "Which is correct to create a function?",
        options: ["function myFunc()", "myFunc() = function", "Function; myFunc()"],
        answer: "function myFunc()",
    },
    {
        question: "which is the correct use of a loop?",
        options: ["loop(let i=0; i<2; i++)", "for(let i=0; i<2; i++)", "goOver(i=0; i++)", "loopOver(array)"],
        answer: "for(let i=0; i<2; i++)",
    },
    {
        question: "How do we declare a comment?",
        options: ["//", "Not possible", "Comment ::", "!...", "<comment>"],
        answer: "//"
    },
    {
        question: "What will be return? a = 9 > 15",
        options: ["Code will not compile", "True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    }

]
export const jsAnswers = []
